trackitdown.net 2009-06-17

# Privacy Statement - Trackitdown - Dance Music Downloads & Merchandise

**Trackitdown.net Privacy Policy**

You may be asked to submit personal information about yourself in order to use the services on the Site. By entering your details on the Site you hereby authorise Trackitdown and its service and content providers to provide you with the services you have selected. All of the information you provide is essential to provide the service you have requested from Trackitdown. Trackitdown will not send you, or authorise any third party to send you, any promotional information unless you specifically opt into our information mailing list which you can subscribe to by clicking <http://www.trackitdown.net/account/profile.php>

When you enter the Site your computer will automatically be issued with a “Cookie”. Cookies are used by many websites in order to track traffic to their sites. Cookies used by Trackittdown are text files that identify your computer to our Server and will only record those areas of the Site that you have visited. You can set your computer so that it will not accept Cookies.

Trackitdown will take all reasonable measures to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under Trackitdown’s control and to ensure that the Site has complied with the provisions of the Data Protection Act 1998 or any other relevant United Kingdom legislation relating to the handling of personal information. If any of the information that you have provided to us changes you must notify us by editing your billing information in Your Account.

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information that Trackitdown holds about you as a result of your use of the Site. A fee of £10.00 is payable for each such request. Please address requests to The Data Protection Officer at Trackitdown.net [info@trackitdown.net](mailto:info@trackitdown.net)

The Site contains links to third party websites. Trackitdown is not responsible for the practices or privacy policy of such third party websites and your use of those third party sites is at your own risk and you consult the relevant terms and conditions of those sites for further information.
